(Bernadette:)Okay.
Thanks, Daddy.
(Bernadette (on phone):)He said the only way to really
fix an old floor like that
(Bernadette (on phone):)is to tear it up
and replace the whole thing.
(Howard:)That sounds expensive.
Hang on.
No offense to her father,
(Raj:)but he's not an
MIT-trained engineer.
(Raj:)Thinking and building
is what you do.
(Howard:)MIT's motto is
"Mind and hand,"
(Howard:)which just so happens was also
my motto as a lonely teenager.
(Raj:)Oh, come on. We just need
to be more creative.
(Raj:)What if you didn't step
on the floor at all?
(Raj:)Like, what if you...
(Raj:)swung on a rope
from the ceiling?
(Leonard:)No.
(Raj:)Okay. Um...
(Raj:)Okay. What if you rig up
a pulley system
(Raj:)and move yourself across
the room in a harness?